("It's Forever" by The Ebonys)
*
Would you like a drink
while you wait?
Uh, yeah, just a little
more water, please.
*
* La la la la la la
Van.
*
(whispering)
Hi, baby.
How are you?
Oh, it's good to see you.
Oh, you too, honey.
You smell good.
-What is that?
-It's Boucheron.
Oh, okay.
I'm gonna try that.
It smells good.
-I'm sorry I'm late.
-No, no, no.
I know you're a working girl.
Don't worry, it's fine.
(giggles)
It's good to see you.
You look really good.
Oh, thank you.
You too.
-Yeah, I like your hair.
-Really?
-Yeah, yeah, it's cute.
-Thanks.
Looks better than
the last time.
Did you go to that shop
I told you to go to?
-Fernando's?
-No.
I went to this place
that I found in Midtown.
Yeah, you should've
went to Fernando's.
Girl, I'm telling you,
he's the best.
He's the best.
-He will fix those roots.
-Hmm.
-Mm-hmm.
-How much does Fernando charge?
-Oh, well, he ain't cheap.
-Okay.
Well, who's paying for yours?
Because I actually
have to pay for mine.
Van, come on.
Come on.
I don't know if you remember
what that's actually like.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
Good evening, ladies.
Can I get you
anything else to drink?
Yeah, actually,
I would like some wine maybe.
Like a Chardonnay.
Why don't we do, like,
a bottle of something?
Do you have something sweet?
-Riesling's good.
-Okay, yeah.
Let's do a bottle of that.
Van, good? Great.
Okay.
-Are you two ready to order?
-Yeah, um...
-I mean, I am, if you are.
-Yeah, it's fine.
I just didn't
want to hold us up.
No, it's fine,
don't worry about it, go ahead.
I'm gonna have
the pad Thai with chicken.
-Excellent.
-Okay.
And, um, I'll go ahead
and do the snapper
and snake bean salad.
-Great choice.
-Yup, great.
-Thanks.
-Be right back.
Thank you.
Oh, Van.
(both laugh)
I'm so glad
I got to catch you.
Yeah, I know.
I know.
-When do you leave tomorrow?
-9:00.
-Oh.
-Yeah.
Damn, that's a short trip.
When did you get in?
You got in, what, yesterday?
-No, day before yesterday.
-You flew Delta?
No, private.
-Oh.
-(laughs)
I mean, yeah.
Yeah, but it wasn't, like,
the nice p.j.,
it was like one of
those rent-a-p.j.'s.
I'm leaving on Delta, though.
-Oh.
-Mm-hmm.
Where you gonna go?
You gonna go home?
Uh, no well, back to New York,
check out this
apartment I like
and then to London.
-London?
-Yep.
-Wow.
-Yeah.
And you're gonna go
with a friend, or--
No, just a special
NBA player friend.
Okay.
I got it, but it's not
the same NBA player...
-Oh, no, girl.
-That you're visiting here?
No, mm-mm, no.
Mm-hmm.
I mean, London's okay,
I guess.
Just too much rain.
Makes my hair frizzy.
Oh, but I love Paris.
Girl, have you been?
I went last month.
Look, let me show you.
Okay, look, look.
There I go in Versailles,
looking like...
looking like
black Marie Antoinette.
(laughs)
It's beautiful.
-Yeah.
-You look beautiful.
You know, you should
come with me next time.
-Girl.
-It'll be fun.
-It'll be fun!
-I have a daughter.
-I can't leave.
-Oh.
That's cute.
You know, sometimes I wish
I had a kid, but then I'm like,
ugh, God no.
You know, I guess when the time
is right, I'll have a kid.
Yeah, I'm sure.
I'm sure as soon as
you find the right guy.
*
-Yeah, the right guy.
-Mm-hmm.
I guess.
-So how have you been?
-So, how's your mom?
-Sorry.
-I'm sorry.
You go, I'm sorry.
How've you been?
I haven't seen you.
I'm, um, I'm busy.
-Yeah?
-I'm busy.
I'm good.
Well, you look great.
-You do, I'm serious.
-Thank you.
Oh, I ran into
Kerry Clopton.
You remember her,
from fifth grade?
- Yeah.
-You know, the girl.
She look like she got a rake
dragged across her face.
(laughs)
On Facebook, it said
she was in a car accident.
*
Here we are.
You know,
can I actually get
some chopsticks
when you get a chance?
-Um...
-Of course.
Yeah, I don't think
we got any.
-Chopsticks?
-What?
Thai people don't use
chopsticks.
(laughs)
I mean, well,
Americans think they do
because they're Asian,
but they don't.
-I just like chopsticks.
-Oh, okay.
Okay.
So what are you doing
after this?
This dude I know, he's having
some, like, listening party--
It sounds cool, but I can't.
I have Lottie.
Oh, come on, Grandma.
Come on, it'll be fun.
I also have work
in the morning.
Yeah, and I have a flight.
-Look, call Earn...
-I'm not calling Earn.
And then have--why?
I don't know, he's busy.
Yeah, I see his Snapchat
sometimes, and he looks...
he looks busy.
Wait, are you...
are you still seeing him?
We have a daughter.
I mean, I still go out, but--
is he living with you?
When he can afford to, yes.
Mmm.
(giggles)
Y'all are funny.
You two are funny.
(laughs)
Oh, okay.
I mean, you used to make fun
of girls like you.
You realize that, right?
No, I'm serious, Van.
You know, you really need
to think about your value.
-I'm sorry?
-Like, what is your value?
Wait, what are you
asking me right now?
Like, why are you
messing around
with this broke-ass nigga?
-Whatever.
-Van.
I know what my worth is.
I don't want to be out here
dating a million football
players--that's your style.
Hey, hey, look.
Women need to be valuable.
Black women
have to be valuable.
Come on, the NBA players
I fuck with,
they fuck with me because
I provide a service,
and I am worth it.
I am cultured, intelligent,
and beautiful.
And that is hard--Van!
Look at me.
That is hard to come by.
That kind of black and white
mentality might work for you,
but for those of us who don't
live on whether a linebacker
-swipes left or right...
-That's not what I'm talking--
On my goddamn ass,
then there's a gray area.
Stop, Van, he's running
around on you, girl.
-Oh, so what?
-What you mean, "So what"?
So what? You don't think
that I'm going out on dates?
You don't think
that I'm running around?
You don't think that I ever
decline his calls
because I have some guy
wrapped around me
with his tongue down my throat?
I mean, come on!
Really?
("The Masquerade"
by George Benson)
Here we go.
*
Enjoy.
* Are we really happy here
* With this lonely game
we play *
*
* Looking for words to say
(camera shutter clicks)
*
* Searching but not finding
Oh, Kevin's here.
-Wait, what?
-Kevin's here.
He's taking us
to the listening launch.
Jayde.
He's got a friend
for you, too.
Cute.
(laughs)
-Hey, baby, how you doing?
-Wait, what?
-Hey, boo.
-Come on, sit down.
-This is my boy, CJ.
-Hey.
-How's it going?
-Hi.
Dang, you looking good.
- You too.
-Well, listen.
-Um, y'all finished, though?
-Yeah.
'Cause we're gonna get ready
and get out of here.
-I'll take the check.
-Okay.
So, hey, sweetheart.
What's your name?
Vanessa.
Okay, okay.
Well, you're looking beautiful.
I'm talking fine
like shine, girl.
I'm gonna go to the bathroom,
okay?
Wait, wait, you're gonna take
your jacket to the bathroom?
Mm-hmm.
*
She's...
It's a girl thing.
*
(sighs)
Hey, pretty girl.
Hi.
I'm sorry.
Van, I'm sorry.
I just wanted to hang out
with my girl tonight,
and I messed up.
I did, okay?
I know I did.
I'm sorry,
please don't leave.
It's fine,
have fun being valuable.
Come on, let's just go to
this listening party
for, like, five minutes.
I told you,
I don't feel like it.
It'll be like old times.
Exactly.
And do you remember that,
in old times,
you always used to hook me up
with the uglier dudes?
(laughing)
Oh, my God.
Okay, CJ is not that bad.
Seriously, I mean,
yeah, he's like--
he's like a lawyer
or something.
I think.
(laughs)
I'm more valuable
than that shit.
You know what?
Hold on.
Look what I got you.
Mm-mm.
I got this just for you.
I know you want it.
Yes, you do.
-No.
-Yes.
-Hell no.
-Yes--hell yes.
I have work in the morning.
No, get your raggedy
purse-having ass
in this car right now.
Come on!
Get in this car.
Get in this car!
You--get in here!
(laughs)
("Oui" by Jeremih)
* Uh
* Uh uh uh-huh
* Uh uh huh
-Yes.
-(giggles)
Yes.
Yup.
What about your friend?
(coughs)
Man, fuck them niggas.
He can wait.
He wants me high.
Believe me.
(chuckles)
-What?
-Shit.
What?
Come on.
Is this that elephant shit
you gave me at Rihanna?
Mm-hmm.
(coughs)
Bitch, it might be.
-(laughs)
-(coughs)
(both giggling)
Oh, man.
-Wait. Oh, wait, wait.
-Give me.
Take a picture of me
real fast.
Take a picture of me real fast.
I'm gonna show you something.
Wait.
Mm.
-You want flash, right?
-Mm-hmm.
-Mm, mm.
-Girl, hold on.
-Go up.
-All right.
*
(camera shutter clicks)
(chuckles)
* Oh yeah, oh yeah
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
I look like--
-Girl.
-I look like I'm fat.
Come on now.
Delete--
erase it.
You look like
an Instagram escort.
(laughs)
You should be proud
of that shit.
*
* I swear your (...)
look best *
I love you, Van.
I love you.
-(giggles)
-I know.
* Oh baby maybe
(laughs)
(cell phone buzzes)
(cell phone continues buzzing)
Oh, fuck.
(cell phone rings)
-Hello?
-Jayde, I'm fucked.
My whole life is fucked.
Okay, your whole life
is not fucked.
-What happened?
-I have a drug test today.
Girl, you smoked yesterday.
-Girl, I'm being serious!
-Me, too.
I don't know
the protocol for this.
I never had a job where
smoking wasn't encouraged.
I don't know,
can you ask someone?
Yeah, let me ask
a friend from the Hawks.
I mean, they get tested,
and he smokes nonstop.
Can you hurry? Because I got
to be at work in two hours.
I'll hurry, all right?
I got you.
Bye.
(cell phone buzzes)
Shit.
(door opens)
EARN: Hey.
It's me.
(door closes)
Hey, what's up?
Hey.
What's wrong?
You look weird.
I'm tired.
-I just had a long night.
-Mm-hmm.
How's Jayde?
She's good.
She's going to New York,
and then she's going to London.
Uh-huh, with who?
I can't keep up.
(chuckles)
Right?
Uh, she eat?
No, not yet.
It's cool,
we'll pick something up.
You sure?
You don't have to do that.
No, no, no.
It's cool.
Maybe you can get, like,
an extra hour of sleep in?
You'll feel better.
-All right.
-Yeah.
Dispatch, we've got a baby
in a residential area,
please advise.
Yeah, she's adorable,
bring backup.
-What is that?
-I don't know.
Hey.
Could I get
Alfred's number?
-Uh, sure.
-Thanks.
What do you need Al for?
Uh, a friend of mine
wants to meet him.
Oh, uh, is it business?
'Cause if it's business, I could
set up that meeting, you know?
-A lady friend.
-Oh, okay.
Matchmaking--
that always goes well.
Here.
I'm taking a shower.
Okay.
What she doing?
I don't know.
-What she doing?
-I don't know.
What she doing?
I don't know.
(coos)
KID (on TV):
King Coco's Crunch-os!
The legend is true!
MAN: Give me that crunch!
(giggles)
(cell phone buzzes)
BOY: But only kids can have
Coconut Crunch-os!
(cell phone buzzes)
MAN: That chocolate-y,
coconut crunch in every bite.
(cell phone buzzes)
Oh, I can almost taste it!
Oh, I got to have
them Crunch-os!
Hello?
Hey, Alfred, um, it's Van.
Okay.
Earn ain't here.
Yeah, I know.
Um...
I need your help.
All right.
I smoked last night.
Smoked what?
Weed.
That thing you sell.
Hey, hey, hey, girl,
I don't sell shit.
You better get off my phone,
talkin' that mess.
How do you pass a drug test?
You smoke?
Yes.
VAN: Alfred,
I am allowed to smoke.
Well, weed is for people who
aren't going anywhere, though.
It's, like, for losers.
AL (on phone): Like, remember?
Listen, I am calling you
because I need your help.
Yeah, yeah,
but I'm petty, right?
I'm Tom Petty.
As much as you be getting
on my ass about smoking, girl?
Alfred, you have to help me.
You know good and well that you
ain't paying Earn any time soon.
Listen, I can't lose my job
because I am all that we have.
VAN: Okay?
Look, my man, Bibby, he buys
piss from somebody
and he put it in a condom
and he tape it to his leg.
I mean, is there anywhere
I could even
buy urine at this point?
Probably not.
Look, I'll ask around for you,
all right?
All right.
- Let me know.
AL: Uh-huh.
("Hit It And Quit It"
by Funkadelic)
*
* I want you to hit it
* Good God hit it and quit it
*
* I want you to
* Whoo whoa yeah
* Oh mama hit it
* God hit it and quit it
*
* I want you to
* Ooh ooh ooh yeah
* Oh mama hit it
* Good God hit it and quit it
*
* I want you to
* Ooh ooh ooh ooh
*
* You can shake it
to the east *
* Shake it to the west
* Hit it
* Good God hit it and quit it
*
* Yeah all up and down
* And move it all around
* Hit it
* Good God hit it and quit it
* Yeah
* You can shake it for dinner
* Or you could spread it
all around *
* Hit it
* Good God hit it and quit it
*
* I want you to hit it
and quit it *
* I want you
to hit it and quit it *
* I want you to hit it
and quit it *
* I want you
to hit it and quit it *
* I want you to hit it
and quit it *
* I want you
to hit it and quit it *
*
* You can shake it
to the east *
* Shake it to the west
* Hit it
* Good God hit it and quit it
*
* You can shake it
Van.
Alicia, hey.
You running ISS today?
Uh, yes, I'm supposed to.
Yeah.
I got Tobias right now.
You want to know
what this boy did?
-Jamilah Hall?
-Here!
-Forrest Hunt?
-Here.
Tobias Walner?
Tobi--
(indistinct chatter)
-Why was he in white face?
-I don't even know.
But he gonna get enough
of fucking with me.
-I know that.
-Um...
Okay, just send him to
Mr. Halford 'cause he loves him.
Somebody needs
to come get him.
I can't do it, Van;
I'm not going to jail today.
Bring Mr. Halford down, and he
will walk him to ISS, okay?
Girl, I got to go.
He gonna get enough.
Watch.
Okay.
Just...
(heartbeat thumping)
(heartbeat continues thumping)
(groans)
Ugh!
(heartbeat continues thumping)
(school bell rings)
(balloon pops)
Fuck!
(intercom buzzes)
Vanessa's here.
Please send her in.
Morning, Ms. Keifer.
I wanted to have
a quick chat with you.
-I didn't receive your sample--
-I smoked weed.
Okay.
Well, urine samples
aren't sent off.
The county can't afford
quarterly drug tests
for its employees,
so after the first one,
they're really just to keep
people on their toes.
Listen, everybody smokes weed.
The system isn't made
for these kids to succeed,
and you got to
shake it off somehow.
-I get it.
-(sighs)
But unfortunately,
you have admitted the use
of an illegal substance
to a superior,
so I've got to fire you.
To cover my own ass,
as well as the school's.
You understand.
Okay, let's say we had
this conversation Friday.
That'll give you the week to
get your things together, okay?
You all right?
Come here.
Yeah, you are.
Whoo!
You are loud.
I mean,
it's all in your hair.
(cell phone buzzes)
(school bell rings)
Hey, Mike.
("Hit It And Quit It"
by Funkadelic)
*
* I want you to hit it
* Good God hit it and quit it
*
* I want you to
* Whoo whoa yeah
* Oh mama hit it
* God hit it and quit it
*
* I want you to
* Ooh ooh ooh yeah
* Oh mama hit it
* Good God hit it and quit it
*
* I want you to
* Ooh ooh ooh ooh
*
* You can shake it
to the east *
* Shake it to the west
* Hit it
* Good God hit it and quit it
*
* You can shake it
to the one... *